

RAWAND ABUAMNA

Executive Secretary & Agile Software Developer

14 years experienced, executive administrative employee, provide high-level administrative support to the Executive Director and other senior staff, dealing with international and local companies and I am an Agile Software Developer, have proficient knowledge in ERP, EPRO and SAP ARIBA. Talented at managing communications relationships and all facets work process in additional to reviewing and interviewing candidates, resolving conflicts onboarding newbies, train junior administrative staff in the department and ensuring that every employee feels he's in the right place.

Abu Dhabi, UAE

rawand.abuamna@gmail.com

00971509297005

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chief Executive Officer Secretary (CEO), Sawaeed Holding P.J.S.C Chief Operating Officer Secretary (COO), Sawaeed Holding P.J.S.C

Abu Dhabi • January 2020 — Present

- Provides high-level administrative support and assistance to the Executive Director and other assigned leadership staff.
- Performs clerical and administrative tasks including drafting letters, memos, invoices, reports, and other documents for senior staff.
- Arranges travel and accommodations for executives.
- Schedules and attends meetings on behalf of executives, taking notes and recording minutes.
- Receives incoming communication or memos on behalf of senior staff, reviews contents, determines importance, and summarizes and/or distributes contents to appropriate staff.
- Performs office tasks including maintaining records, ordering supplies, and performing basic bookkeeping.
- Performs additional duties as assigned by executives.
- Performs other related duties as assigned.

Customer Service Specialist, Sawaeed Holding P.J.S.C

Abu Dhabi • February 2019 – December 2019

- Strategy and business development.
- Manage large amounts of incoming phone calls
- Identify and assess customers' needs to achieve satisfaction.
- Build sustainable relationships and trust with customer accounts through open and interactive communication.
- Provide accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods.
- Handle customer complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits; follow up to ensure resolution.
- Keep records of customer interactions, process customer accounts and file documents.
- Follow communication procedures, guidelines and policies.

Operations Coordinator, Sawaeed Employment L.L.C

Abu Dhabi • June 2018 - January 2019

- Facilitating cross-channel feedback from customers and employees to management and executive teams.
- Working with team leaders, managers, and department heads to learn departmental needs and goals.
- Ensuring that all activities conform to local, industry and company standards.
- Observing, reviewing and analyzing processes to identify inefficiencies and areas where improvements could be made.
- Identifying and resolving any problems in the mobilizations process.

Administrative Coordinator, Sawaeed Employment L.L.C

Abu Dhabi • May 2012 – May 2018

- Manage and route phone calls appropriately.
- Process and report on office expenses.
- Maintain physical and digital employee records.
- Schedule in-office and external meetings.
- Distribute incoming mail.
- Manage and order office supplies.
- Make travel arrangements.
- Organize company documents into updated filing systems.
- Address employees' and clients' queries (via email, phone or in-person).
- Prepare presentations, spreadsheets and reports.
- Update the office policies as needed.

Logistics Coordinator, Al Sahraa Holding Group

Abu Dhabi • September 2009 – December 2011

- Coordinating transportation providers to ensure prompt and proper movement of shipments.
- Responding to customer inquiries and referring clients to the proper channels.
- Reviewing purchase orders and shipping documents to ensure accuracy.
- Making special shipping arrangements as necessary.
- Tracking and fixing shipping errors.
- Preparing bills and invoices.
- Managing distribution and shipment budgets.
- Ensuring that the quality of all services provided meets the required standards.
- Developing processes that make the supply chain more efficient and organized.
- Analyzing and optimizing logistical procedures.

ABILITIES

- Excellent verbal and written communication skills.
- Excellent organizational skills and attention to detail.
- Excellent time management skills with a proven ability to meet deadlines.
- Ability to function well in a high-paced and at times stressful environment.
- Extensive knowledge of office administration, clerical procedures, and recordkeeping systems.
- Able to type minimum of 50 words per minute.
- Extremely proficient with Microsoft Office Suite and similar software with the ability to learn updated software.

SKILLS

- Communication
- Computer Skills
- **Detail-Oriented**
- **Human Resources Information Software**
- Interviewing
- Multi-Tasking
- Organization
- **Payroll Management**

EDUCATION

Abu Dhabi University – Abu Dhabi

BA: Mass communication and media

GPA: 3.30

British Council - Abu Dhabi

IELTS: Academic

GPA: 6.0

Udacity – Dubai

NANODEGREE: Agile Software Development

CERTIFICATIONS

College Of Medicine and Health Sciences -**UAEU**

Basic Clinical Skills Course For Healthcare Assistants

Eton Institute

Building Relationships for success in sales

Eton Institute

Overcoming Objections to path the sales

Spearhead Training

Customer Service database

Emirates Foundation

Time Management

Emirates Foundation

Developing the integrated strategy

TRA Academy

Digital and social media marketing

PERSONAL DETAIL

Marital Statas: Single

Date of Birth: 25 August 1990

Nationality: Palestinian – Employment Visa Work Type: Full-Time Employment Contract

- Problem-Solving
- Professionalism
- Project Management
- Research Skills
- Scheduling
- Workers' Compensation
- Writing Skills

American Language Center – Abu Dhabi

ADVANCED: General English Course

GPA: Proficient

Al Marfa'a School – Western

LITERARY: High School Diploma

GPA: 73.2

TRA Academy

Creative thinking

Emirates Foundation

Entrepreneurship development

Resources High field Qualifications International Accreditation

Course in international Emergency First Aid, level 2

Emirates Foundation

Course in Advanced First Aid

Abu Dhabi Police

Trained and equipped to deal with certain medical Emergencies

Abu Dhabi Police

Course in police initiative

Volunteering Experience

UAE Volunteer Institutions

LANGUAGES

English: Fluent Arabic: Native